I count myself lucky to live in the relative calm of the countryside, a safe distance away from the chaos and claustrophobia of city life.
我觉得自己很幸运，能生活在相对宁静的乡村，与城市生活的混乱和幽闭恐惧保持着安全的距离。
However, I have to venture into the urban jungle every day to work and it's then that I realise how rude city dwellers can be.
然而，我每天都得冒险进入城市丛林去工作，这时我才意识到城市居民可能有多无礼。
Maybe I'm being unfair.
也许我有失公允。
Not everyone comes from the city - many of us commute from somewhere else and, together with a large number of tourists, we are all squeezed into this small space - so it's no surprise that we get irritable and hot under the collar.
并非每个人都来自城市——我们很多人从其他地方通勤而来，再加上大量的游客，我们都挤在这个狭小的空间里——所以我们变得烦躁不安、怒气冲冲也就不足为奇了。
Competing for a space on the Tube train or bus is only one of the reasons that makes us grumpy.
在地铁或公交车上争抢座位只是让我们变得脾气暴躁的原因之一。
Our rush to get into the office and home again means we have no time to make conversation with other people: we are driven by efficiency.
我们急着去办公室，然后又急着回家，这意味着我们没有时间和其他人交谈：我们被效率所驱使。
Thomas Farley, writer and broadcaster explains that, "We're in a rush, we're off to a meeting, to a luncheon... and I don't think it's a bad thing, I just think we need to be mindful that it's not a deliberate disregard or somebody's trying to be rude on purpose."
作家兼播音员托马斯·法利解释说：“我们很匆忙，要去参加会议、去吃午餐……我认为这并不是一件坏事，我只是觉得我们需要留意，这并不是故意的轻视，也不是有人故意无礼。”
So we are not trying to be rude, we just have something important on our mind to think about.
所以我们并不是故意无礼，只是我们心里想着一些重要的事情。
Cities can, however, be scary places - especially if you're not used to them and this can make us reluctant to start a conversation.
然而，城市可能是令人害怕的地方——尤其是如果你不习惯它们的话，这会让我们不愿意开始交谈。
We might be hyper-vigilant thinking that the person next to us is going to kill us or worse still, get into conversation with us!
我们可能会高度警惕，认为旁边的人会伤害我们，或者更糟糕的是，会和我们交谈！
Dr Elle Boag, a social psychologist at Birmingham City University, agrees that people can view cities as threatening places.
伯明翰城市大学的社会心理学家埃尔·博阿格博士也认为，人们会把城市视为有威胁的地方。
She says, "We're persistently looking for potential threats around us, and this then makes us not give eye contact, this will reduce the likelihood that anybody will say hello."
她说：“我们一直在寻找周围潜在的威胁，这就导致我们不与他人进行眼神交流，这会降低有人打招呼的可能性。”
She calls this our 'protective mechanism' which is another way that makes us appear antisocial.
她把这称为我们的“保护机制”，这是另一种让我们看起来不爱交际的方式。
Perhaps if we did start talking more to each other we may realise that our fellow train or bus passenger is actually quite normal with the same concerns and that if you have to grin and bear the pressures of city life, at least you can do it together.
也许如果我们开始更多地相互交谈，我们可能会意识到，和我们同坐火车或公交车的乘客其实也很正常，有着同样的担忧，而且如果你不得不默默忍受城市生活的压力，至少你可以和他人一起承受。
In London, a group called 'Talk to me London' is trying to encourage just that.
在伦敦，一个名为“和我聊聊，伦敦”的组织就在努力鼓励人们这样做。
They have created 'Tube Chat' badges which you can wear to show you're happy to talk to a stranger.
他们制作了“地铁聊天”徽章，你可以佩戴它来表明你愿意和陌生人交谈。
But of course, you may choose to live in the city in order to be anonymous - to blend in with the crowd - and not have to talk to people!
但当然，你可能选择住在城市是为了保持匿名状态——融入人群中——而不必和人交谈！
Maybe that's the benefit of living in the city: you can be who you like - and as rude as you like.
也许这就是住在城市的好处：你可以成为你想成为的人——并且可以随心所欲地无礼。
Do you think people in your city seem to be rude?
你觉得你所在城市的人看起来无礼吗？